<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2">
  <channel>
    <title>Ahmed Alnabhan Project2 RSS Feed</title>
    <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/project2.rss</link>
    <description>RSS Feed of Ahmed's websites fro project2</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <LastUpdated>Thur. Mar, 3 2012 16:45</LastUpdated>
    <item>
      <title>Serena sails through, Venus crashes out </title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>Serena Williams marked her first European appearance of the season with victory on the Madrid Open's striking blue clay courts on Monday, but her sister Venus crashed out in the second round.&#xD; &#xD; Holder Petra Kvitova also started well as the third seed defeated New Zealander Marina Erakovic 6-2 6-3.&#xD; &#xD; Towering Czech Kvitova beat Victoria Azarenka in the final last year before going on to win the Wimbledon title.&#xD; &#xD; The only seeded player to fall was number 15 Jelena Jankovic who went out to Spanish wildcard Carla Suarez 4-6 7-6 6-4 in the first round.&#xD; &#xD; Serena Williams, who reached the third round the last time she played in Madrid in 2010, powered past last week's Budapest Grand Prix runner-up Elena Vesnina of Russia 6-3 6-1.&#xD; &#xD; The ninth seed delivered some powerful serves, hitting 14 aces to set up a meeting with another Russian, Anastasia Pavlyuchenkova, in the next round.&#xD; &#xD; &amp;quot;I was feeling good,&amp;quot; Williams told reporters. &amp;quot;It's my first tournament in Europe this year and I just hope I can keep up the good form,&amp;quot; added the American who has yet to lose in eight clay outings this season.&#xD; &#xD; &amp;quot;I haven't noticed a difference between the blue and the red clay. I think it's the same, it's just you don't get as dirty,&amp;quot; added Williams.&#xD; &#xD; Venus entered Madrid on a wildcard as she started her third tournament after seven months out suffering with Sjogren's Syndrome, an auto-immune disease which causes fatigue and joint soreness.&#xD; &#xD; The former world number one struggled past Romania's Simona Halep in three sets on Saturday, but crumpled against stronger opposition on Monday falling 6-4 6-1 to 12th seed Angelique Kerber of Germany.&#xD; &#xD; Kerber, 24, is in the midst of her breakout season with both her career title coming in 2012&#xD; &#xD; China's Li Na, the eighth seed, joined Kerber in the last 16 with a straightforward victory over Spanish wildcard Silvia Soler-Espinosa 6-3 6-1.&#xD; &#xD; Czech qualifier Andrea Hlavackova and compatriot Lucie Hradecka, Italian Sara Errani, Russia's Ekaterina Makarova, and Estonia's Kaia Kanepi also made it through to the second round.&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>May 7, 2012, 8:26 pm</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots lineman Light retires after 11 NFL seasons</title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>New England Patriots left tackle Matt Light, one of only five players to start in five Super Bowls, officially retired on Monday during a ceremony in Foxborough, Massachusetts.&#xD; &#xD; The retirement of the 33-year-old Light left New England quarterback Tom Brady as the only current Patriot to have been on the team's roster for each of their three Super Bowl wins and five trips in all to the title game since the 2001 season.&#xD; &#xD; Light, who played 11 NFL seasons, said he wanted to leave the game in good health and spend more time with his children.&#xD; &#xD; &amp;quot;On the field, (Light) was a tenacious competitor who had one of the toughest jobs,&amp;quot; Patriots owner Robert Kraft said at the ceremony. &amp;quot;Every week he's (been) going up against the greatest athlete on the defensive (line) who was coming after our quarterback's blindside.&amp;quot;&#xD; &#xD; Light, a three-time Pro Bowler chosen by the Patriots in the second round of the 2001 NFL draft out of Purdue, played his entire NFL career with New England.&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>May 7, 2012, 8:25 pm</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knicks' Chandler named Defensive Player of the Year</title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>New York Knicks center Tyson Chandler was named the NBA's Defensive Player of the Year on Wednesday, the first player from the storied franchise to win the award.&#xD; &#xD; Chandler received 311 points, including 45 first-place votes, to beat out Oklahoma City Thunder swingman Serge Ibaka, who finished second with 294 points.&#xD; &#xD; Orlando Magic center Dwight Howard, who had won the award each of the previous three seasons, finished third with 186 points.&#xD; &#xD; With the 7-foot-1 (2.16m), 240-pound (108.9kg) Chandler patrolling the paint, the Knicks ranked second in opponent turnovers per game (17.0), 10th in opponent field goal percentage (.442), and 11th in opponent scoring (94.7).&#xD; &#xD; "To me, it's a team thing," Chandler told a news conference. "I'm here to accept this as an individual but it's definitely a team award."&#xD; &#xD; Chandler, an 11-year NBA veteran who played last season with the champion Dallas Mavericks, averaged 11.3 points and 9.9 rebounds this season.&#xD; &#xD; The award was chosen by a panel of 121 sportswriters and broadcasters in the United States and Canada.&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>May 2, 2012, 9:47 pm</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>test</title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>&lt;script&gt;alert('hi');&lt;/script&gt;&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>May 1, 2012, 11:01 am</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clippers silence Thunder to end playoff drought </title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>The streaking Los Angeles Clippers knocked Oklahoma City out of first place in the West with a forceful 92-77 victory on Monday that earned the hosts a first playoff berth in six years.&#xD; &#xD; Nick Young led a balanced attack with 19 points off the bench, Blake Griffin added 17 and 11 rebounds and the Clippers overwhelmed the visiting Thunder in the second half to reach the post-season for the first time since the 2005-06 campaign.&#xD; &#xD; ?"It feels great, especially to do it against one of the top teams in the league," Young told reporters. "?I was too excited (after the game). I ran to the back and was slapping hands with everyone."&#xD; &#xD; Winners in 12 of their last 14 games, the Clippers (38-23) also have a shot at their first ever division title, trailing the Lakers by a game in the Pacific Division, and for third in the West.&#xD; &#xD; The Thunder (44-17), meanwhile, slipped percentage points behind San Antonio in their see-saw tussle for the top seed in the conference.&#xD; &#xD; Kevin Durant had a team-high 24 points for Oklahoma City, who built a nine-point halftime lead before being outscored 49-25 in the second half.&#xD; &#xD; It was their second defeat at the hands of the Clippers in less than a week following a two-point loss last Wednesday.&#xD; &#xD; In the latest showdown, Los Angeles scored the game's first basket and did not lead again until the fourth quarter, and as the Clippers warmed up to pull away, the Thunder suddenly went cold and shot just 37 percent on the night.&#xD; &#xD; All-Star Russell Westbrook had a particularly off game and finished with just nine points.&#xD; &#xD; Chris Paul tallied 12 and 10 assists. His arrival to the Clippers through an off-season trade, combined with the team's other roster moves, signaled new promise for a franchise that has endured too many losing seasons.&#xD; &#xD; ?"It means a lot for us (to make the playoffs) but we can't be complacent, we have to keep pushing forward and want more," Griffin said. "?We still have a lot of work to do."&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>April 20, 2012, 10:13 am</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamilton posts fastest time in free practice for Bahrain Grand Prix</title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>World championship leader Lewis Hamilton on Friday posted the fastest time in the first free practice for Sunday's Bahrain Grand Prix.    Hamilton, who has a two point lead from his team-mate Jenson Button, managed a time of one minute 33.572 seconds for the 5.412 kilometre-long lap, beating world champion Sebastian Vettel by 0.305 seconds.    Force India's Paul di Resta had the third fastest time.    Mercedes' Nico Rosberg, who won the last race in China, had the fourth-fastest time.    A second free practice session will be held later Friday, with qualifying on Saturday and the race on Sunday.&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>April 20, 2012, 10:10 am</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kahn impressed by Dortmund's appetite for victory </title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>Few players showed greater aggression and hunger for victory than Oliver Kahn, yet even the former Germany and Bayern Munich goalkeeper is impressed by Borussia Dortmund's will to win.&#xD; &#xD; Dortmund, eight points clear of Bayern at the top of the Bundesliga, can wrap up their second successive league title on Saturday with two games to spare with a home win against fourth-placed Borussia Moenchengladbach (1630).&#xD; &#xD; Kahn was particularly impressed by the way Dortmund defender Never Subotic ran up behind Arjen Robben and shouted at him after the Bayern's Dutch winger missed a late penalty in last week's match between the two sides, which Dortmund won 1-0.&#xD; &#xD; "That is exactly the kind of mentality you need, it expresses the unlimited will to win," Kahn told Sport Bild magazine in an interview. "It says: 'I want to win the title at any price.'&#xD; &#xD; "What is striking for me is the hunger for success and the huge identification that (coach) Juergen Klopp and the team have with the club," Kahn added.&#xD; &#xD; The 42-year-old also tipped Dortmund to beat Bayern for a fifth time in a row when the two meet again in the German Cup final at the end of the season.&#xD; &#xD; "I have my doubts whether the Bayern players can deal with that defeat positively, and that they may lose a fifth game in a row," he said.&#xD; &#xD; Kahn was involved in a number of memorable matches against Dortmund during his playing days, and the sight of the yellow and black team seemed to bring out the most aggressive in him.&#xD; &#xD; The low point came when he aimed a flying kick at Dortmund forward Stephane Chapusiat, bit Heiko Herrlich on the neck and pulled Andreas Moeller's ear during an action-packed match in 1999.&#xD; &#xD; Kahn added that Dortmund's presence could benefit Bayern in the long term.&#xD; &#xD; "Competition means that you are always being asked questions and that you will never be allowed to get sluggish or lazy," he said.&#xD; &#xD; For the second season running, Dortmund's young team, orchestrated by their charismatic coach Juergen Klopp, have taken the Bundesliga by storm with their intense, non-stop, physical game.&#xD; &#xD; The general consensus is that they have wanted the title more than arch-rivals Bavarians, whose eyes are fixed on the Champions League and the possibility of playing in the final in their own Allianz Arena stadium.&#xD; &#xD; Dortmund, who looked upon the Champions League as a chance to gain international experience, finished bottom of their group, leaving them to concentrate on domestic football.&#xD; &#xD; The 44-year-old is known for his exuberant celebrations and Germany is already braced for his performance on Saturday if, as expected, they wrap up the title.&#xD; &#xD; Dortmund, who are playing in the evening game, may even have clinched the title before kickoff if Bayern fail to win their match away to Werder Bremen (1330).&#xD; &#xD; That match falls in between the two legs of their Champions League semi-final against Real Madrid, with Bayern having won the first leg 2-1 at home last Tuesday.&#xD; &#xD; At the other end, hapless Kaiserslautern (20 points) will be relegated if they fail to beat Hertha Berlin (28) in a clash of the two bottom sides (Saturday 1330), or if Cologne pick up a point at home to VfB Stuttgart (Saturday 1330).&#xD; &#xD; Four points adrift of 15th-placed Augsburg, Cologne will be happy to settle for 16th place, which would lead them into to a two-leg playoff against a team from the second division.&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>April 20, 2012, 12:18 am</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arsenal midfielder Arteta out for the season - reports</title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>Mikel Arteta will miss the rest of Arsenal's season with an ankle ligament injury, British media reported on Thursday.&#xD; &#xD; The Spanish midfielder, who has played an influential role in Arsenal's improved form in recent weeks, hurt his ankle while attempting a cross in the early stages of Monday's 2-1 defeat to Wigan Athletic at the Emirates Stadium.&#xD; &#xD; Arteta received treatment off the pitch - during which time Wigan scored their second goal - but he could not continue. Scans showed the ankle was not broken but the ligament damage was bad enough to keep him out for Arsenal's final four Premier League matches.&#xD; &#xD; Arsenal manager Arsene Wenger, whose side face Chelsea at home in the league on Saturday, now has a gap to fill in midfield as he is without long-term absentee Jack Wilshere and Abou Diaby, who is not match fit.&#xD; &#xD; Yossi Benayoun, on loan from Chelsea, is ineligible to play against his parent club.&#xD; &#xD; Arsenal are third, five points ahead of their arch-rivals Tottenham Hotspur who have a game in hand.&#xD; &#xD; After facing Chelsea this weekend, Arsenal go to Stoke City, then play Norwich City at home before ending their campaign at West Bromwich Albion.&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>April 20, 2012, 12:07 am</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meyer says respects Fourie's decision on unavailability </title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>South Africa coach Heyneke Meyer said on Thursday that he understood star centre Jaque Fourie's reasons for making himself unavailable for the Springboks this year.&#xD; &#xD; The 29-year-old Fourie, who has been capped 69 times for South Africa since 2003, announced on Wednesday that he was unavailable for the Springboks while he completes the second year of his contract with Japanese club Kobelco Steelers.&#xD; &#xD; "I respect Jaque's thoughts in not making himself available but it's a pity because he's close to being the best outside centre in the world and he was definitely an integral part of my plans," Meyer told reporters in Pretoria.&#xD; &#xD; "But it's very important that the players I choose are focused on the South African cause and want to play for the Springboks. If there's pressure from their overseas clubs, then I understand," Meyer told reporters in Pretoria on Thursday.&#xD; &#xD; The new Springboks coach said the door was not closed to Fourie to make a return ahead of the 2015 World Cup.&#xD; &#xD; "I'd like to speak again with Jaque in two years time, because we'll be going into our World Cup plans and I hope he can still be there then," he said.&#xD; &#xD; Meyer, who had just completed the first of three planning camps with potential Springbok players, drawn from the Cheetahs and the Lions, said there was plenty of talent at his disposal to replace senior players who were not available.&#xD; &#xD; "The absence of players like Jaque is great for the youngsters and even the more experienced guys," he said.&#xD; &#xD; "I've told the players that even if they're 29 and haven't yet played for the Springboks, that they still have a chance of being chosen."&#xD; &#xD; "There were one or two players at this camp that I haven't worked with before and I can see that they are great players. There's enough depth in South African rugby," Meyer added.&#xD; &#xD; "I've had one-on-ones with every player and they know where they stand and I now understand their roles in their franchises and why they do certain things. I have much more insight into them, which is great, and they know exactly what I want."&#xD; &#xD; Former Blue Bulls and Leicester coach Meyer said he had concerns over the number of injuries to experienced Springboks who were potential successors to retired captain John Smit.&#xD; &#xD; "There've been a lot of injuries - guys like Schalk Burger, Juan Smith and Jean de Villiers are all out of action - while there's been speculation about Victor Matfield playing again.&#xD; &#xD; "I'll announce the captain the week before the first England test and he'll be captain only for those three tests."&#xD; &#xD; Meyer announced a list of 45 players from the Bulls and Sharks, who both have SuperRugby byes next week, to attend the second planning camp in Pretoria from Sunday to next Thursday.&#xD; &#xD; (Editing by Martyn Herman)&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>April 19, 2012, 11:56 pm</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pizarro transfer to Bayern finalized</title>
      <link>http://people.rit.edu/~amn5948/739/project2/news.php</link>
      <description>A Munich newspaper reported Thursday that Claudio Pizarro's move from Werder Bremen to Bayern Munich has been finalized.    The M&#xFC;nchner Merkur said that the 33-year-old was already looking for accommodation in the Bavarian capital.    It would be the second time that the Peruvian international joins Bayern Munich from Werder Bremen, having already played for Bayern between 2001 and 2007, winning the World Club Cup title, as well as three German league championships and cup competitions.    Pizarro has refused to confirm the report, telling journalists after Bremen's training on Thursday: "I will not say anything about that."    Munich has been mulling over Pizarro's return for a few months. He could be an alternative for Germany striker Mario Gomez, pushing Ivica Olic, who is considering moving to VfL Wolfsburg, down in the pecking order.    Pizarro, who is the top foreign goalscorer in the German Bundesliga with 158 goals in 330 matches, gave notice on his contract at the end of March and can leave Bremen on a free clearance at the end of this season.    "We are trying to get this matter settled as soon as possible. We have made Pizarro a very good offer," Bremen manager Klaus Allofs said.&#xD;
</description>
      <pubDate>April 19, 2012, 11:10 pm</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
